[Music]
I am Jasmine, one of the people who
is part of Prudential Syariah. My
daily life starts from here,
chatting with the hustle and bustle of the capital
in the morning.
[Music] The
office's location in the city center is an
advantage for me because it can be reached by
almost all modes of public transportation.
[Music]
Here we instill the value of humility.
Almost everyone in the
Prudential Syariah environment greets each other every time they
meet.
[Music]
[Applause]
Protecting and helping each other
has become a value held by
all elements of Prudential Syariah.
And these are my colleagues. Well,
this is my workplace, where I usually
do my office work.
[Music]
This comfortable working space helps
me be productive in my work.
[Music]
Hello, good afternoon everyone.
Today,
[Music]
Not only the people, the facilities in
this office are very well supported with
adequate facilities and infrastructure so that
work becomes easy and practical.
Everyone has the same opportunity
here. They can give
feedback to each other regardless of
position. That is one manifestation
of the value of fairness and transparency.
Okay,
how can it be
[Music]
as one of the supporting pillars for
Sharia producers, of course, providing
justice for consumers and employees
is the main thing, thank you
[Music]
friends, because this is the call to prayer, let's
click first, okay?
[Music]
togetherness is something that always
surrounds our daily lives in the office, this is
possible because of the values ​​of
humility and togetherness that are instilled
[Music]
I am grateful to be able to contribute and
live all the values ​​according to
the beliefs that I have
[Music]
Waalaikumsalam Yes, I'm about to go home, being
a part of
Prudential Syariah gives me many
opportunities to learn and develop
because here we work in a
warm environment without exception
[Music]
to achieve one goal that is certain
to make something happen